A Guide to the Papers of Harry Walter Roberts 1921,1970
Johnston Memorial Library, Virginia State University
- Organizations and Affiliations
  - Alpha Phi Alpha Fraternity
    - National Reports 1962 (Box-folder 31:2)
    - Southern Regional Annual Reports 1962 (Box-folder 31:3)
    - Report of the General Secretary 1962 (Box-folder 31:4)
    - Report on Standards 1962 (Box-folder 31:5)
    - Annual Report Western Regional V.P. 1962 (Box-folder 31:6)
    - Midwestern Region Annual Reports 1962 (Box-folder 31:7)
    - Correspondence 1932 (Box-folder 31:8)
    - General Correspondence 1950, 1962 (Box-folder 31:9)
    - Alpha Beta Boule' A 1958 (Box-folder 31:10)
    - Alpha Beta Boule' B 1958 (Box-folder 31:11)
    - Alpha Beta Boule' D 1958 (Box-folder 31:12)
    - Alpha Beta Boule' H 1958 (Box-folder 31:13)
    - Alpha Beta Boule' F 1958 (Box-folder 31:14)
    - Alpha Beta Boule' I 1958 (Box-folder 31:15)
    - Alpha Beta Boule' M 1958 (Box-folder 31:16)
    - Alpha Beta Boule' N 1958 (Box-folder 31:17)
    - Alpha Beta Boule' P 1958 (Box-folder 31:18)
    - Alpha Beta Boule' R 1958 (Box-folder 31:19)
    - Alpha Beta Boule' S 1958 (Box-folder 31:20)
    - Alpha Beta Boule' T 1958 (Box-folder 31:21)
    - Alpha Beta Boule' W 1958 (Box-folder 31:22)
    - Alpha Phi Alpha- Housing Foundation Report (Box-folder 31:23)
  - The Virginia Voters League
    - VVL Constitution 1941 (Box-folder 32:1)
    - VVL Correspondence 1941 (Box-folder 32:2)
    - VVL Correspondence 1955 (Box-folder 32:3)
    - VVL Correspondence April, 1961 (Box-folder 32:4)
    - VVL Correspondence May, 1961 (Box-folder 32:5)
    - VVL Correspondence June, 1962 (Box-folder 32:6)
    - VVL Correspondence March, 1963 (Box-folder 32:7)
    - VVL Correspondence October-December, 1963 (Box-folder 32:8)
    - VVL Correspondence January-May, 1964 (Box-folder 32:9)
    - VVL Newsletter 1960 (Box-folder 32:10)
    - VVL Newsletter 1961 (Box-folder 32:11)
    - VVL Newsletter 1962 (Box-folder 32:12)
    - VVL Programs 1961-1962 (Box-folder 32:13)
    - VVL Flyer, Luther Porter Jackson Day 1951 (Box-folder 32:14)
    - VVL Flyers (Box-folder 32:15)
    - VVL, SCLC, Flyers Forms (Box-folder 32:16)
    - The Voting Status of Negroes in Virginia 1950-1951 (Box-folder 32:17)
    - Correspondence-The NAACP 1965-1966 (Box-folder 32:18)
  - The NAACP
    - NAACP Printed 1965-1966 (Box-folder 32:19)
    - NAACP 1965-1966 (Box-folder 32:20)
    - Crusade for Voters 1965 (Box-folder 32:21)
    - Flyers-NAACP (Box-folder 32:22)
    - Programs-NAACP (Box-folder 32:23)
  - The Summer School for Ministers
    - Sub-Committiee of Rural Ministers-Minutes of Meetings (Box-folder 33:1)
    - The Conference of Negro College on Rural Life-Report 1946, 1948 (Box-folder 33:2)
    - Report on Recreation for Ministers (Box-folder 33:3)
    - General Correspondence 1943-1946 (Box-folder 33:4)
    - General Correspondence 1947-1948 (Box-folder 33:5)
    - General Correspondence 1949-1950 (Box-folder 33:6)
    - High School Completion Exams 1945 (Box-folder 33:7)
    - Rural Church-Lunenburg, Virginia 1947 (Box-folder 33:8)
    - General Material 1949 (Box-folder 33:9)
    - Planning Summer School 1950 (Box-folder 33:10)
    - Mailing List (Box-folder 33:11)
    - Related Projects (Box-folder 33:12)
    - Press Releases (Box-folder 33:13)
    - Resolutions 1949 (Box-folder 33:14)
    - Rural Virginia Survey (Box-folder 33a:1)
    - Rural Virginia Survey (notes) (Box-folder 33a:2)
    - Schedules (Box-folder 33a:3)
    - Bibliography (Box-folder 33a:4)
    - Activities (Box-folder 33a:5)
    - Brochure (Box-folder 33a:6)
    - Church and Race Ministers (Box-folder 33a:7)
    - Course Materials (Box-folder 33a:8)
  - The League of Colored People
    - Meeting Agendas 1933-1934 (Box-folder 34:1)
    - Correspondence 1933-1936 (Box-folder 34:2)
    - Printed 1933-1934, n.d. (Box-folder 34:3)
    - Printed "The Marxist Society" (Box-folder 34:4)
    - Programs (2) The African Society, World Friendship League (Box-folder 34:5)
    - Membership List (Box-folder 34:6)
    - Photographs (Box-folder 34:7)
    - The Keys October 1933 (Box 34)
    - The Keys (5) January 1934 (Box 34)
    - The Keys (2) April-June, 1934 (Box 34)
    - The Keys (2) July-September, 1934 (Box 34)
    - The Keys October-December, 1934 (Box 34)
    - The Keys January-March, 1935 (Box 34)
    - The Keys July-September, 1937 (Box 34)
    - The Keys October-December, 1937 (Box 34)
    - The Negro in the Future July 13-15, 1934 (Box 34)
    - The Journal of Living and Learning February 1934 (Box 34)
    - WASU (Preach) March 1934 (Box 34)
    - British Information Services May 1945 (Box 34)
- The Department of Sociology
  - Annual Reports
    - Sociology Annual Reports 1947-1952 (Box-folder 35:1)
    - Sociology Annual Reports 1952-1956 (Box-folder 35:2)
    - Sociology Annual Reports 1957-1958 (Box-folder 35:3)
    - Sociology Annual Reports 1959-1960 (Box-folder 35:4)
    - Sociology Annual Reports 1960-1961 (Box-folder 35:5)
    - Sociology Annual Reports 1961-1962 (Box-folder 35:6)
    - Sociology Annual Reports 1962-1963 (Box-folder 35:7)
    - Sociology Annual Reports 1965-1966 (Box-folder 35:8)
  - Department Correspondence by folder headings
    - Economic Opportunity Council of Petersburg (Box-folder 35:9)
    - Special Institute 1967 (Box-folder 35:10)
    - University Chrsitian Mission Correspondence 1950-1951, 1954 (Box-folder 35:11)
    - Univeristy Christian Mission Report 1951 (Box-folder 35:12)
    - Roberts/Science Research Company 1950-1951 (Box-folder 35:13)
    - Research Study (Voting) 1958 (Box-folder 35:14)
    - The National CMA (Colored Merchants Associations) (Box-folder 35:15)
    - Superintendent Public Instruction (U.S.) May 16- June 7 1961 (Box-folder 35:16)
    - Superintendent Public Instruction March-May 15, 1961 (Box-folder 35:17)
    - U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics (Box-folder 35:18)
  - Correspondence By Date
    - Correspondence January 1934-February 1935 (Box-folder 36:1)
    - Correspondence March-July 1935 (Box-folder 36:2)
    - Correspondence August-December 1935 (Box-folder 36:3)
    - Correspondence January-February 1936 (Box-folder 36:4)
    - Correspondence March-April 1936 (Box-folder 36:5)
    - Correspondence May-August 1936 (Box-folder 36:6)
    - Correspondence 1939-1940 (Box-folder 36:7)
    - Correspondence 1941-1944 (Box-folder 36:8)
    - Correspondence 1945 (Box-folder 36:9)
    - Correspondence January-March 1946 (Box-folder 36:10)
    - Correspondence April-June 1946 (Box-folder 36:11)
    - Correspondence July-December 1946 (Box-folder 36:12)
    - Correspondence January-April 1947 (Box-folder 36:13)
    - Correspondence May-September 1947 (Box-folder 36:14)
    - Correspondence October-December 1947 (Box-folder 36:15)
    - Correspondence January-March 1948 (Box-folder 37:1)
    - Correspondence April-May 1948 (Box-folder 37:2)
    - Correspondence June-December 1948 (Box-folder 37:3)
    - Correspondence January-March 1949 (Box-folder 37:4)
    - Correspondence April-May 1949 (Box-folder 37:5)
    - Correspondence June-July 1949 (Box-folder 37:6)
    - Correspondence August-October 1949 (Box-folder 37:7)
    - Correspondence November-December 1949 (Box-folder 37:8)
    - Correspondence January-February 1950 (Box-folder 37:9)
    - Correspondence March 1950 (Box-folder 37:10)
    - Correspondence April 1950 (Box-folder 37:11)
    - Correspondence May 1950 (Box-folder 37:12)
    - Correspondence June-August 1950 (Box-folder 37:13)
    - Correspondence September 1950 (Box-folder 37:14)
    - Correspondence October-Decmember 1950 (Box-folder 37:15)
    - Correspondence January-February 1951 (Box-folder 38:1)
    - Correspondence March-April 1951 (Box-folder 38:2)
    - Correspondence May-July 1951 (Box-folder 38:3)
    - Correspondence August-September 1951 (Box-folder 38:4)
    - Correspondence October-December 1951 (Box-folder 38:5)
    - Correspondence January-March 1952 (Box-folder 38:6)
    - Correspondence April 1952 (Box-folder 38:7)
    - Correspondence May-June 1952 (Box-folder 38:8)
    - Correspondence July 1952 (Box-folder 38:9)
    - Correspondence October 1952 (Box-folder 38:10)
    - Correspondence January-February 1953 (Box-folder 39:1)
    - Correspondence March 1953 (Box-folder 39:2)
    - Correspondence April 1953 (Box-folder 39:3)
    - Correspondence May 1953 (Box-folder 39:4)
    - Correspondence June-July 1953 (Box-folder 39:5)
    - Correspondence August 1953 (Box-folder 39:6)
    - Correspondence September 1953 (Box-folder 39:7)
    - Correspondence October 1953 (Box-folder 39:8)
    - Correspondence November-December 1953 (Box-folder 39:9)
    - Correspondence January 1954 (Box-folder 39:10)
    - Correspondence February 1954 (Box-folder 39:11)
    - Correspondence March 1954 (Box-folder 39:12)
    - Correspondence May 1954 (Box-folder 39:13)
    - Correspondence June 1954 (Box-folder 39:14)
    - Correspondence July-September 1954 (Box-folder 39:15)
    - Correspondence October 1-12, 1954 (Box-folder 39:16)
    - Correspondence October 18, 1954 (Box-folder 39:17)
    - Correspondence November-December 1954 (Box-folder 39:18)
    - Correspondence January 1955 (Box-folder 40:1)
    - Correspondence February 1955 (Box-folder 40:2)
    - Correspondence March 1-8, 1955 (Box-folder 40:3)
    - Correspondence March 19-31, 1955 (Box-folder 40:4)
    - Correspondence April 1955 (Box-folder 40:5)
    - Correspondence May 1955 (Box-folder 40:6)
    - Correspondence June 1955 (Box-folder 40:7)
    - Correspondence July 1955 (Box-folder 40:8)
    - Correspondence August 1955 (Box-folder 40:9)
    - Correspondence September 1955 (Box-folder 40:10)
    - Correspondence October 1955 (Box-folder 40:11)
    - Correspondence November 1955 (Box-folder 40:12)
    - Correspondence Decmeber 1955 (Box-folder 40:13)
    - Correspondence January 1956 (Box-folder 41:1)
    - Correspondence February 1956 (Box-folder 41:2)
    - Correspondence March 1956 (Box-folder 41:3)
    - Correspondence April 1956 (Box-folder 41:4)
    - Correspondence May 1956 (Box-folder 41:5)
    - Correspondence June 1956 (Box-folder 41:6)
    - Correspondence July 1956 (Box-folder 41:7)
    - Correspondence August 1956 (Box-folder 41:8)
    - Correspondence September 1956 (Box-folder 41:9)
    - Correspondence October 1956 (Box-folder 41:10)
    - Correspondence November 1956 (Box-folder 41:11)
    - Correspondence December 1956 (Box-folder 41:12)
    - Correspondence January 1957 (Box-folder 42:1)
    - Correspondence February 1-16, 1957 (Box-folder 42:2)
    - Correspondence February 17-28, 1957 (Box-folder 42:3)
    - Correspondence March 1-9, 1957 (Box-folder 42:4)
    - Correspondence March 15-31, 1957 (Box-folder 42:5)
    - Correspondence April 1-15, 1957 (Box-folder 42:6)
    - Correspondence April 16-30, 1957 (Box-folder 42:7)
    - Correspondence May 1957 (Box-folder 42:8)
    - Correspondence June 1957 (Box-folder 42:9)
    - Correspondence July 1-9, 1957 (Box-folder 42:10)
    - Correspondence July 10-31, 1957 (Box-folder 42:11)
    - Correspondence August 1959 (Box-folder 42:12)
    - Correspondence September 1959 (Box-folder 42:13)
    - Correspondence October 1959 (Box-folder 42:14)
    - Correspondence November 1959 (Box-folder 42:15)
    - Correspondence December 1959 (Box-folder 42:16)
    - Correspondence January 1960 (Box-folder 43:1)
    - Correspondence February 1960 (Box-folder 43:2)
    - Correspondence March 1960 (Box-folder 43:3)
    - Correspondence April 5-16, 1960 (Box-folder 43:4)
    - Correspondence April 18-25, 1960 (Box-folder 43:5)
    - Correspondence May 1960 (Box-folder 43:6)
    - Correspondence June 1960 (Box-folder 43:7)
    - Correspondence July 1960 (Box-folder 43:8)
    - Correspondence August 1960 (Box-folder 43:9)
    - Correspondence September 1960 (Box-folder 43:10)
    - Correspondence October 1960 (Box-folder 43:11)
    - Correspondence November 1960 (Box-folder 43:12)
    - Correspondence December 1960 (Box-folder 43:13)
    - Correspondence January 1961 (Box-folder 44:1)
    - Correspondence February 1961 (Box-folder 44:2)
    - Correspondence March 1961 (Box-folder 44:3)
    - Correspondence April 1961 (Box-folder 44:4)
    - Correspondence May 1961 (Box-folder 44:5)
    - Correspondence June-July 1961 (Box-folder 44:6)
    - Correspondence August 1961 (Box-folder 44:7)
    - Correspondence September 1961 (Box-folder 44:8)
    - Correspondence October 1961 (Box-folder 44:9)
    - Correspondence Novmeber 1961 (Box-folder 44:10)
    - Correspondence December 1961 (Box-folder 44:11)
    - Correspondence January 1962 (Box-folder 44:12)
    - Correspondence February 1962 (Box-folder 44:13)
    - Correspondence March 1962 (Box-folder 44:14)
    - Correspondence April 1962 (Box-folder 44:15)
    - Correspondence May 1962 (Box-folder 44:16)
    - Correspondence June 1962 (Box-folder 44:17)
    - Correspondence July-August 1962 (Box-folder 44:18)
    - Correspondence September-October 1962 (Box-folder 44:19)
    - Correspondence November-December 1962 (Box-folder 44:20)
    - Correspondence January 1963 (Box-folder 45:1)
    - Correspondence February 1963 (Box-folder 45:2)
    - Correspondence March 1963 (Box-folder 45:3)
    - Correspondence April 1963 (Box-folder 45:4)
    - Correspondence May-June 1963 (Box-folder 45:5)
    - Correspondence July 1963 (Box-folder 45:6)
    - Correspondence August 9-16, 1965 (Box-folder 45:7)
    - Correspondence August 17-27, 1965 (Box-folder 45:8)
    - Correspondence September-October 1965 (Box-folder 45:9)
    - Correspondence Novmeber-December 1965 (Box-folder 45:10)
    - Correspondence January-February 1966 (Box-folder 45:11)
    - Correspondence March-April 1966 (Box-folder 44:12)
    - Correspondence May-June 1966 (Box-folder 45:13)
    - Correspondence July 1966 (Box-folder 45:14)
    - Correspondence January-February 1967 (Box-folder 46:1)
    - Correspondence March-April 1967 (Box-folder 46:2)
    - Correspondence May-June 1967 (Box-folder 46:3)
    - Correspondence July-September 1967 (Box-folder 46:4)
    - Correspondence October-November 1967 (Box-folder 46:5)
    - Correspondence December 1967 (Box-folder 46:6)
    - Correspondence January-February 1968 (Box-folder 46:7)
    - Correspondence March 1968 (Box-folder 46:8)
    - Correspondence April 1968 (Box-folder 46:9)
    - Correspondence May-November 1968 (Box-folder 46:10)
    - Correspondence September 1974 (Box-folder 46:11)
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 46:12)
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 46:13)
  - Sociology Graduates
    - Graduates October 28 1938-December 7, 1939 (Box-folder 47:1)
    - Graduates January 26, 1940-June 17, 1941 (Box-folder 47:2)
    - Graduates July 8, 1941-December 27, 1942 (Box-folder 47:3)
    - Graduates January 8, 1943-December 11, 1943 (Box-folder 47:4)
    - Graduates January 9, 1944-December 12, 1944 (Box-folder 47:5)
    - Graduates January 10, 1945-December 18, 1945 (Box-folder 47:6)
    - Graduates January 23, 1946-December 7, 1946 (Box-folder 47:7)
    - Graduates January 7, 1947-October 22, 1947 (Box-folder 47:8)
    - Graduates February 10 1948-July 8 1948 (Box-folder 47:9)
    - Graduates July 9, 1948-September 20, 1948 (Box-folder 47:10)
    - Graduates September 24, 1948-December 20, 1948 (Box-folder 47:11)
    - Graduates (Box-folder 47:12)
  - Notes on the History of the Sociology Department
    - Correspondence 1957 (Box-folder 48:1)
    - Notes in History of Sociology Department 1958 (Box-folder 48:2)
    - Correspondence 1961 (Box-folder 48:3)
    - Correspondence March-April 10, 1962 (Box-folder 48:4)
    - Correspondence April 10-28, 1962 (Box-folder 48:5)
    - Correspondence May-June 1962 (Box-folder 48:6)
    - Correspondence 1966 (Box-folder 48:7)
  - HBCU, Graduates in the TVA States 1941-1950
    - The Indian Woods Community TVA 1955 (Box-folder 48:8)
    - TVA Correspondence April 1959 (Box-folder 48:9)
    - TVA Correspondence May-December 1959 (Box-folder 48:10)
    - TVA Correspondence January-May 1960 (Box-folder 48:11)
    - TVA Correspondence July-August 1960 (Box-folder 48:12)
    - TVA Correspondence February-November 1962 (Box-folder 48:13)
- Literary
  - Diary 1932, 1966 (Box 49)
  - Articles
    - The Personal Method, Servicemen 1959 (Box-folder 49:1)
    - Disadvantage Factors March 1944 (Box-folder 49:2)
    - The Life and Labor of Rural Virginia Negroes 1942 (Box-folder 49:3)
    - The Rural Negro Minister 1947 (Box-folder 49:4)
    - Writing-Interracial Marriage 1947 (Box-folder 49:5)
    - The Rural Negro Minister: His Work and Slavery 1947 (Box-folder 49:6)
    - The Rural Negro Minister: His Educational Status 1948 (Box-folder 49:7)
  - Thesis and Dissertation
    - "The Influence of External Relations Upon the Inner Life of Social Groups" (Box 50)
    - Introduction Table of Contents (Box-folder 51:1)
    - Attitude, Parents Toward Farm Life (Box-folder 51:2)
    - Auxiliary, School, Community League-Political Behaviors (Box-folder 51:3)
    - Auxiliary School Organizations (Box-folder 51:4)
    - Cash Tenants (Box-folder 51:5)
    - Education (Box-folder 51:6)
    - Foods and Nutrition (Box-folder 51:7)
    - Fraternal Orders (Box-folder 51:8)
    - Fraternal and Mutual Associations (Box-folder 51:9)
    - Fraternal Benefits Societies Domicile in Virginia (Box-folder 51:10)
    - Living Conditions (Box-folder 51:11)
    - Making the School A Community Center (Box-folder 51:12)
    - Negro Rural Population (Box-folder 51:13)
    - Recreation ans Leisure Time (Box-folder 51:14)
    - Sharecroppers (Box-folder 51:15)
    - Their Work and its Research-Part III (Box-folder 51:16)
    - Their Work and Its Research-Part III (Box-folder 51:17)
    - Their Work and its Research (Box-folder 51:18)
    - The Auxiliary School Organization (Box-folder 51:19)
    - The Rural Negro Church and Religious Life (Box-folder 51:20)
    - Their Living and Their Instutution-Part IV (Box-folder 51:21)
    - Urban and Rural Life (Box-folder 51:22)
    - The Aftermath of Slavery The Negroes Social Heritage (Box-folder 52:1)
    - The Aftermath of Slavery the White's Social Heritage (ALS) (Box-folder 52:2)
    - The Organ Growth Introduction (Box-folder 52:3)
    - Their Work and its Research (Box-folder 52:4)
    - Institution of Slavery and Plantations Economy (Box-folder 52:5)
    - The Institution of Slavery (Box-folder 52:6)
    - Church Conditions Garnette and Poulton (Box-folder 52:7)
    - Libraries and Black Students (Box-folder 52:8)
- Research Data
  - Dissertation Research
    - Suggested Revisions in Roberts Paper on Negro Servicemen (Box-folder 52:9)
    - War Time Education (Box-folder 52:10)
    - Emotional and Behavior Problems (Box-folder 52:11)
    - Paper World War II (Box-folder 52:12)
    - Racial Attitudes (Box-folder 52:13)
    - Report on Social Problems (Box-folder 52:14)
    - Research White Soldiers (Box-folder 52:15)
    - The effects of Military Service-Black about whites (Box-folder 52:16)
    - The Mental Ability (white) (Box-folder 52:17)
    - The Negro Soldier in the Past (Box-folder 52:18)
    - Venereal Disease (Box-folder 52:19)
    - The White Social Hierarchy (Box-folder 52:20)
    - White Interviews (Box-folder 52:21)
    - Interviews-White Soldiers (Box-folder 52:22)
    - Research-White Soldiers (Box-folder 52:23)
    - Prior Service Attitude of Black Soldiers (Box-folder 52:24)
    - Case Study-Beaverdam (Box-folder 53:1)
    - Case Study-Beaverdam (Box-folder 53:2)
    - Case Study-Branchville, Southhampton Co. (Box-folder 53:3)
    - Camp Lee Situation (Box-folder 53:4)
    - Research-Change in Acreage of Farm Managers (Box-folder 53:5)
    - Research-Chatham Negroes (Box-folder 53:6)
    - Case Study- The Cypress Community (Box-folder 53:7)
    - Research-The Curriculum (Box-folder 53:8)
    - Case Histories- Dinwiddie County (Box-folder 53:9)
    - Education-Dinwiddle County (Box-folder 53:10)
    - Research-Evaluating A School System (Box-folder 53:11)
    - Farm Study (Box-folder 53:12)
    - Farm Study (Box-folder 53:13)
    - Nansemond County (Box-folder 53:14)
    - Nansemond County Community Map (Box-folder 53:15)
    - Research-Nansemond County (Box-folder 53:16)
    - Research-Nansemond County (Box-folder 53:17)
    - Study-Petersburg, Va. 1960 (Box-folder 53:18)
    - Study Petersburg Va. Study on Poverty (Box-folder 53:19)
    - Study-Pittsylvania County (Box-folder 53:20)
    - Study Pittsylvania County (Box-folder 53:21)
    - Research-Present Educational Status (Box-folder 53:22)
    - Report-Rural Health (Box-folder 53:23)
    - Rural Communities Problem (Box-folder 53:24)
    - Research-Sharecroppers (Box-folder 53:25)
    - Research-The Slave Plantation System (Box-folder 53:26)
    - Sold to Georgia (Box-folder 53:27)
    - Southampton County (Box-folder 53:28)
    - Questionnaire-Southern Education (Box-folder 53:29)
    - The Committee of Odell Walker (Box-folder 53:30)
    - Walker Grant (Box-folder 53:31)
    - Research-The White Heritage (Box-folder 53:32)
  - The Jerome Davis Papers
    - Diary November 3-December 31, 1916 (Box 54)
    - Correspondence 1917-1920 (Box-folder 54:1)
    - Correspondence 1925-1926 (Box-folder 54:2)
    - Correspondence 1941 (Box-folder 54:3)
    - Correspondence 1942 (Box-folder 54:4)
    - Correspondence 1945 (Box-folder 54:5)
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 54:6)
    - Worlds First Proletarian Church 1932 (Box-folder 54:7)
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 54:8)
    - Chronicle May 1917 (Box-folder 54:9)
    - Chronicle June 1927 (Box-folder 54:10)
    - Manifesto of Anarchists Communist 1919 (Box-folder 54:11)
    - Brief-Anani Nazarczuk November 6, 1919 (Box-folder 54:12)
    - Legal Brief-Ivan Poliachok November 1919 (Box-folder 54:13)
    - Deported-Walter Borisuk 1919 (Box-folder 54:14)
    - Writing (Box-folder 54:15)
    - The Communist Party-Printed (Box-folder 54:16)
    - European Russian Tour (Czechoslovakia) 1961 (Box-folder 54)
    - Columbia Conserve Co. 1926 (Box-folder 55:1)
    - Columbia Conserve Co.-Stockholders 1933 (Box-folder 55:2)
    - Columbia Conserve Co.-Counsel Meeting 1932 (Box-folder 55:3)
    - Columbia Conserve Co.-Correspondence and Counsel Meeting 1932 (Box-folder 55:4)
    - Columbia Conserve Co.-Special Counsel Meeting 1933 (Box-folder 55:5)
    - Columbia Conserve Co. February 3, 1933 (Box-folder 55:6)
    - Columbia Conserve Co.-Special Counsel Meeting January 1933 (Box-folder 55:7)
    - Columbia Conserve Co.-Minutes Regular Executive Committee July 1936 (Box-folder 55:8)
    - Columbia Conserve Co.-Correspondence December 1932 (Box-folder 55:9)
    - Columbia Conserve Co.-Correspondence February 1933 (Box-folder 55:10)
    - Columbia Conserve Co.-Correspondence March 1-15, 1933 (Box-folder 55:11)
    - Columbia Conserve Co.-Correspondence March 16-31, 1933 (Box-folder 55:12)
    - Columbia Conserve Co.-Correspondence April 3-18, 1933 (Box-folder 55:13)
    - Columbia Conserve Co.-Correspondence April 19-31, 1933 (Box-folder 55:14)
    - Columbia Conserve Co.-Correspondence May 20-31, 1933 (Box-folder 55:15)
    - Columbia Conserve Co.-Correspondence May 8-12, 1933 (Box-folder 55:16)
    - Columbia Conserve Co.-Correspondence May 15-19, 1933 (Box-folder 55:17)
    - Columbia Conserve Co.-Correspondence June 1933 (Box-folder 55:18)
    - Columbia Conserve Co.-Correspondence July 1933 (Box-folder 55:19)
    - Columbia Conserve Co.-Correspondence August-September 1933 (Box-folder 55:20)
    - Columbia Conserve Co.-Correspondence October-December 1933 (Box-folder 55:21)
    - Columbia Conserve Co.-Correspondence February 1931 (Box-folder 55:22)
    - Columbia Conserve Co.-Flyer 1925 (Box-folder 55:23)
- Photographs
  - Family, Personal, Business
    - "Y" Youth Conference 1938 (Box-folder 56:1)
    - Graduates, VSU 1951 (Box-folder 56:2)
    - Alpha Beta Boule' 1946 (Box-folder 56:3)
    - Alpha Phi Alpha Members (Box-folder 56:4)